[
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who%20developed%20Python%20Programming%20Language?",
    "correct_answer": "Guido%20van%20Rossum",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Wick%20van%20Rossum",
      "Rasmus%20Lerdorf",
      "Niene%20Stom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which%20type%20of%20Programming%20does%20Python%20support?",
    "correct_answer": "all%20of%20the%20mentioned",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "object-oriented%20programming",
      "structured%20programming",
      "functional%20programming"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20the%20correct%20extension%20of%20the%20Python%20file?",
    "correct_answer": ".py",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      ".python",
      ".pl",
      ".p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "How%20is%20a%20code%20block%20indicated%20in%20Python?",
    "correct_answer": "Indentation",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Brackets",
      "Key",
      "None%20of%20the%20above"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "All%20keywords%20in%20Python%20are%20in",
    "correct_answer": "None%20of%20the%20mentioned",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Capitalized",
      "lower%20case",
      "UPPER%20CASE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which%20keyword%20is%20used%20for%20function%20in%20Python%20language?",
    "correct_answer": "Def",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Function",
      "Fun",
      "Define"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20character%20is%20used%20to%20give%20single-line%20comments%20in%20Python?",
    "correct_answer": "#",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "//",
      "!",
      " /*"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Python%20supports%20the%20creation%20of%20anonymous%20functions%20at%20runtime,%20using%20a%20construct%20called",
    "correct_answer": "lambda",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "pi",
      "anonymous",
      "none%20of%20the%20mentioned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which%20of%20thefollowing%20is%20not%20a%20core%20data%20type%20in%20Python%20programming?",
    "correct_answer": "Class",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tuples",
      "Lists",
      "Dictionary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Python",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which%20one%20of%20the%20following%20is%20not%20a%20keyword%20in%20Python%20language?",
    "correct_answer": "eval",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "pass",
      "assert",
      "nonlocal"
    ]
  }
]